mg8.biz 2015-12-18

# Addicting games - Playing best FREE addicting games on Mg8.biz

## Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy is to inform our users of the information that we collect, what we use it for, how we use it and under what circumstances (if any) we disclose it.

We respect the personal privacy of each and every visitor to our website. We only collect and use information as specified in this Privacy Policy. Visitors enter our site without having to declare any information, and our server automatically recognizes no information from visitors regarding domain or email address.

The information that we collect is used by [Mg8.biz](http://mg8.biz/) only to serve as information to improve website content and to notify website updates. Collected information is never shared to any other organizations for any purposes.

Visitors enter [Mg8.biz](http://mg8.biz/) and enjoy games without registration or declaration. 

Some sections and services of our website may require registration for better personalization and experience. Such registration will require users to give certain information that is kept within our user database only and is never disclosed or shared to any other organizations for any purposes. The information is used only to contact users about services that he/she is interested in and has registered for.

Some sections and services may ask users to give additional information such as demographic information (income, gender, education, etc.) and identifiers (username, password, etc.). However, these are only optional. Such information can help expand the user experience and enhance personalization, but is not required. 

Our advertisements, surveys and newsletter are published through users’ and subscribers’ email address, which is never shared or sold. You can set this optional feature on or off within user’s panel.

Any change or adjustment to Privacy Policy will be clearly disclosed in this privacy statement.

If users have any disputes, complaints, inquiries, or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us via our contact form.
